Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.17 01:39:05
前情回顾
[Narrator] Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
病人的名字?
- [Bailey] Patient's name! - How many times...
-我告诉你多少次了不要来烦我当我在... - ellis grey.
- [Yang] Ellis Grey. - Meredith's mother.
-Meredith的妈妈. -问题不在于是那个Burke和我分手了,
It's not that Burke broke up with me, it's how he broke up with me.
而在于他是如何向我提出分手的.
Have you even told Burke about the baby?
劳烦你和 burke说一下孩子的事好不好?
Cristina!
-Cristina! -是宫外孕.
[Addison] It's an extrauterine pregnancy.
-她大量出血. -不要装做是我男友的样子和我说话.
Stop talking to me like you're my boyfriend! Stop talking to me at all.
再也不要和我说话.
If you came here to try to win me back, forget about it.
如果你出现在这里是为了重新得到我,
-你不用想了. -我只知道我还爱着你.
I just know I still love you.
恨你是最令人精疲力尽的事.
Hating you is the most exhausting.
能在外科实习期生存的关键
[Meredith] The key to surviving a surgical internship is denial.
是否认.
We deny that we're tired, we deny that we're scared,
我们否认疲劳.
我们否认恐惧.
we deny how badly we want to succeed,
我们否认我们有多么想成功.
最重要的是, 我们否认我们在否认.
and most importantly, we deny that we're in denial.
我不知道.当我离开的时候, cristina 说她很好.
When I left, Cristina said she was OK.
没有人经历过她所经历的事， 并且现在能完全放下.
Nobody goes through what she did and is totally over it by now.
Cristina可以.
- Cristina can. - She's fine.
-她很棒. -过于棒了.她这是冷酷.
Too fine. She's cold.
并不是这样，她是个中坚分子 她只是在纹理中放了些冰块而已
No, she's hardcore. She's got ice in her veins.
她做了所有她该做的.
- She does what she has to do to. - She lost a baby.
她失去了孩子. 她失去了输卵管.
And a fallopian tube. She acts like she doesn't care.
但她表现得一点都不关心.
She's all "Hello, I'm totally fine."
她完全就是个只说"你好, 我很好"的人.
She's my friend too but she's acting like she has no emotions or warmth,
虽然她也是我的朋友, 但是她表现得就像是
她没有感情和热情, 像是没有灵魂一样.
like she's missing a soul.
上帝啊,她会成为一位伟大的外科医生的.
- God, she's gonna make a great surgeon. - George!
-George. -这是真的.
It's true. You show no weakness, you make it to the top.
如果你不示弱, 你就能成为最强的.
有些人仅仅是把他们的感情留给自己.
Some people just keep their feelings to themselves.
我们仅仅看到我们想看到的
[Meredith] We only see what we want to see
相信我们想信的.
and believe what we want to believe.
确实是这样的.
And it works.
我们老是在骗自己,
We lie to ourselves so much that, after a while,
而过了一会儿,这些谎言开始看上去像真理的一样了.
the lies start to seem like the truth.
Meredith吻了我.
Meredith kissed me. Addison kissed me.
Addison吻了我.
My wife and my girlfriend kissed me on the same day.
我的妻子和女朋友都吻了我
-在同一天. -Joe...我看上去对你友好吗?
Joe, do I look friendly to you?
你是个充满欢乐和博爱的小女人.
Oh. Yeah, you're a tiny little kitten of joy and love.
-怎么啦? -他救了我的命.
- What? He saved my life. - His first mistake.
这是第一个错误
McDreamy, go sit by someone who cares.
美梦先生, 找关心你的人谈心去.
[Meredith] We deny so much that we can't recognize the truth,
我们否认得太多了
以至于不能辨认
就在我们眼前的真相.
right in front of our faces.
一些都会好起来的.
Everything's gonna be fine. Addison'll go back to New York.
Addison会回到纽约去,
meredith和我会重新开始.
Meredith and I will start over, everything's gonna be fine. Right?
一些都会好起来的,对吗?
你可真是蠢的无可救药了.
You so damn stupid.
我要你们今天每个人都全神贯注.
[Bailey] I want everyone focused.
cristina不在,我们少了一个人,
With Cristina out, we're short an intern and I feel it will be one of those days.
而且我有预感以后几天也会是这样.
- And, Karev, see the chief today. - What for?
karev, 下班之前去看看头儿.
为什么?
Do I look psychic to you? He's the chief. He asked. You go.
你以为我是你精神领袖吗?
他是你的上司，他让你去你就去.
- What did he do now? - Maybe he gave the chief syphilis.
他这次又怎么了?
可能把梅毒传染给了头儿吧.
当我们在柏力滋丛林中的时候,
So we're in the middle of the Belizian jungle and this jaguarondi
一只美洲豹突然跳了出来
jumps out and bites one of the guides.
咬住其中一个导游.
They all look at me. They're yelling, "You're a doctor, help him!"
所有人都看着我
他们大声喊,"你是博士，救救他"
我突然发现“博士”在这一刻没一点好处.
This is one time a Ph.D. Does no good.
打扰一下，我是不是错过了什么社科课的铃声?
I'm sorry, did I miss the bell for social hour?
-不过是个传教士生涯的小故事. -你是传教士?
- Missionary tales. - You're a missionary?
我不是，我父母是. 我们旅行很多地方，他们现在还在旅行.
No, my parents. We traveled a lot. They still do.
Oh, wow.这个挺棒的.
Wow. This stuff is great.
Um, 这位是Burke医生的病人...
Um, this is Dr. Burke's patient, Kalpana Vera...
-kalpana vera. -Kalpana.
"Kull-punnah." Named by villagers in Nepal.
名字是尼泊尔一个地方的村名帮我取的.
Presents with multiple syncopal episodes and ventricular arrhythmias.
Uh, 她的症状是多重间歇性昏厥
并伴有心律不齐.
- So you've been passing out? - And having palpitations.
这么说你曾昏倒过?
没错，有时候还有心悸.
History of rheumatic heart disease with mitral valve stenosis.
以前曾患有风湿性心脏病 以及二尖瓣狭窄
他们需要把我装上船，从赞比亚运回来
They had to ship me from Zambia to the States
那时候我只有8岁，整整治了3个月.
for three months of treatment when I was eight. Rheumatic fever almost killed me.
风湿热差点就要了我的命.
Dr. Stevens. What are the primary causes of ventricular arrhythmias?
Stevens医生, 导致心律不齐的 最主要原因是什么?
心血管疾病,二尖瓣下垂, 外界刺激, 吸毒
Valvular disease, mitral valve prolapse,
stimulants, drugs, and metabolic abnormalities.
以及新陈代谢紊乱.
[PA] Scrub nurse to OR Six.
怎么了?
- What? - Out.
出去.
- I'm fine. - Out!
-我没事. -出去.
You better be in your room by the time we round on you.
你最好呆在你的病房里 当我们巡视到你那里的时候.
什么时候呢?
- And when will that be? - In fifteen seconds.
15秒之后.
-14... 13...12... 11... -内裤真可爱, yang.
Fourteen, thirteen, twelve, eleven...
- Nice panties, Yang. - [Giggling]
做你的梦去...坏蛋.
In your dreams, Evil Spawn.
cristina yang.
Cristina Yang. Post-op day three from a unilateral salpingectomy.
入院三天,刚做完 单输卵管切除...
并且已经做好重返工作岗位的准备.
- And ready to get back to work. - Is she?
她行吗?
I'm taking solids and my pain is controlled with oral meds. I'm ready.
我已经可以吃固体食物了
同时口服止痛药对我 就很有效用了，我准备好了.
Didn't the nurse say this morning you had a fever?
今早的那个护士 不是说你发烧了吗？
妈.
- Mother. - Cristina, did you have a fever?
Cristina,你发过烧吗?
体温最高到101度(华氏),有什么了不起啊?
Temp spiked to 101 last night. Big deal.
上个月她工作的两个 夜班中曾发烧到102度
She worked two shifts with a 102 degree flu.
是啊,太对了 george.非常感谢.
Yes. Exactly, George. Thank you.
我们感激你的奉献,
And we appreciate your dedication, but you stay in bed until it normalizes.
但是你现在要躺在床上,直到一切稳定下来.
我不知告诉她多少次了
I keep telling her there's more to life than surgery and career.
好多东西比医生和事业更重要.
Go upholster something.
妈,去搞搞装修吧.
Look, I need you to relax, shut up, and get better.
-听着,你现在给我放松下来, -把嘴闭上,快点好起来.
这周你是病人 那下周你就可以做医生了
You're a patient this week so you can be a doctor next week.
明白?
Mer. You cannot leave me alone with her.
Mere.
你不能让我单独和她呆在一起.
I am flying over the cuckoo's nest here. Save me.
她快把我逼疯了 注解:"One flew over the cuckoo's nest"是一部电影 讲一个精神病院的故事
-你必须救我. -你需要时间疗养.
- You need time to heal. - I'm healed. I'm healed!
我已经好了,全好了!
Oh, 天.
Oh, God.
好 O'malley医生,你来报告.
OK, Dr. O'Malley, you're presenting.
Okay, Grey医生,手术后第三天..
OK, Dr. Grey is post-op day three from a tumor resection.
是肿瘤切除
Wrong, wrong, wrong. He's got it all wrong.
不对,不对,不对.
他全搞错了 根本就不是哮喘, 是gerd(胃食管倒流症).
It's not asthma, it's GERD. He needs a Nissen fundoplication.
他需要做尼森治愈术
- I don't want her in the room. - Mom!
-我不想在这里看见她. -妈.
她是孩子, 我不想她和我一起工作.
She's a child and I won't have her on my team.
一会出去见你,Grey医生.
We'll meet you outside, Dr. Grey.
[PA] Dr. Marash to Cardiology. Dr. Marash to Cardiology.
你在到处闲逛吗?
- Skipping rounds? - Avoiding mother.
躲避我妈.
Meredith...
- You've got a wife. - Yes.
你已经有老婆了.
- Your life is complicated. - Yes.
对.
-你的生活很复杂. -嗯,对.
I don't need complicated. I have complicated all on my own.
我不想要复杂.
-我有一堆自己的乱摊子. -对.
别再说对了.
- Yes. - Stop saying yes.
尽量不再让事情恶化.
I'm trying not to make any sudden movements.
-你觉得有趣吗?. -Addison要走了.
- You think this is funny? - Addison's leaving.
她在这医院里 没有任何患者了.
She doesn't have any more patients here.
再也没有任何原因让她留下来了.
- There's no reason for her to be here. - No reason?
没有原因?
None whatsoever.
无论什么.
Well now, isn't this cozy?
哇,真爽啊你们,嗯?
带我一个呗,
Can I join in or are you not into threesomes?
除非你们不喜欢3P?
[PA] Dr. Shannon, 1436.
我要走了.
- I have to go. - Meredith...
Meredith...
你真是个魔鬼.
You really are Satan. You realize that, right?
你自己也意识到了对吗?
If Satan were to take physical form, he'd be you.
如果魔鬼有具体形态的话 他一定是你,
-任何地方,任何时间. -我根本不是.
- Everywhere, all the time. - I am so not Satan.
你怎么还没骑上 你的破扫帚
Why haven't you gotten on your broomstick and left?
飞回你应该去的纽约?
- Stop being petty. - Stop being an adulterous bitch.
-你能不这么卑鄙吗? -你能不做偷汉子的婊子吗?
[Elevator bell]
你明白最终你还是会 原谅我的,对吗?
You are going to forgive me eventually?
我是说,你只是不能...
You can't just...
我的意思是,你需要时间
There was a time you thought of me as your best friend?
来思考我才是你 最好的朋友.
There was a time when I thought you were the love of my life.
曾经有一刻
我认为你是我今生的挚爱.
Things change.
不过一切都变了.
离婚协议.
Divorce papers.
你律师说这个可以.
Your lawyer said they're OK. I haven't signed them yet.
我还没签字.
The ball's in your court. If you sign, I'll sign.
你有发球权 你签字的话,我就签
I'll sign and be on the first plane out of here.
我签字之后会坐 最快的航班离开这里.
I'll sign them immediately. I want you out of here soon.
我立刻就签.
我要你尽快离开这里.
Derek, 你有想过吗? 即使我真的是魔鬼
Derek, have you ever thought that, even if I am Satan and an adulterous bitch,
又背着你偷汉子
that I still might be the love of your life?
但是我可能还是你生命中的挚爱?
[& Psaap: Crazy in the Rocket]
nobody knows were they might end up
nobody knows
oh, oh
suppose you'll never know
[Gulls cry]
[Steady beeping]
[Sighs] It's my chart.
我的病历.
You're the patient. Not the doctor. Act like one.
你是病人,不是医生.
做个病人.
我了解你一个人很孤独.
- It's been tough finding you alone. - Yeah? Well...
是啊..
- How are you doing? - You have my chart. You tell me.
你好吗?
-嗯,你拿着我病历呢,你说呢 -你好吗?
How are you doing?
我很好,好的不能再好了.
I'm fine. Perfectly OK.
我有权利知道.
- I had a right to know. - Well, now you do.
-嗯,现在你知道了 -Cristina...
- Cristina... - Look. Now you know. It's over.
听着,你现在知道了,一切都结束了.
和你没有关系,
There's nothing for you to deal with. So what else is there left to say?
所以我不知道.
- Plenty. For starters... - Oh, look. It's my mother.
还有什么可以说的
-很多,作为开头,你可以重新和我... -哦,看,这是我妈妈
Preston burke医生. 很高兴认识你,yang太太
Dr. Preston Burke. Nice to meet you, Mrs. Yang.
事实上,是rubenstein.
Actually it's Rubenstein.
Saul rubenstein医生来自beverly hills,
Dr. Saul Rubenstein of Beverly Hills? The oral surgeon?
口腔医生,我又再婚了.
I'm remarried. Been remarried since Cristina was, what? About three?
再婚的时候,cristina大概只有.. 几岁,3岁?
妈,你说太多话了.
Mom, that's too much information, he has other things to do.
他还有其他事情要做呢.
你长的挺帅.他挺帅.
You're good-looking. He's good-looking.
为什么你从来不带一个 像他这么帅的男生回家?
Why don't you ever bring home a man as good-looking as him?
-别说了. -怎么了?
- Stop. - What?
-别再说了. -Cristina!别介意她.
- Stop talking. - Cristina. Forgive her.
我不知道我到底做了什么
I don't know what I ever did to raise such an unpleasant girl.
怎么养出一个这么讨厌的丫头.
- Oh, me? I'm unpleasant? - Excuse me.
Oh, 我, 讨厌...我让人讨厌?
失陪一下.
-你知道他是谁吗? -谁?
- Do you know who that was? - Who?
他是我的..他是我的老板.
- That was my boss! - I only said nice things.
-我对他不错啊. -为什么你说我是讨厌的?
Why'd you call me unpleasant in front of my boss?
还在我老板面前?
Lighten up, please.
放轻松,宝贝.
OK, I was thinking that maybe we might want to... you might...
Okay, 我在想,也许 我们可以..
你可以...
- OK, we both have tonight off so... - You are so into me.
okay, 我们俩今晚都休息,所以..
你追我可挺紧的啊.
- Shut up. - It's sad. The worship. The adoration.
闭嘴.
真难过...崇拜,爱慕.
我还这么帅,把你迷倒了.
And I'm so handsome, I intoxicate you.
Okay, 你知道吗?没事了.
OK, you know what? Forget it.
Izzie, 你今晚愿意 和我一起出去吗?
Izzie, would you like to go out with me tonight?
约会?
On a date? And you wear something gorgeous, I pay for food...
你打扮漂亮点,我请你吃饭.
你在拿我开心是吗?
- Are you making fun of me? - I'm not making fun of you.
我没有.
OK, then.
那好吧.
- Good. - Good.
好.
I said I never wanted to see you again.
我以为告诉过你 再也不想见到你了
'Cause you're too lazy to learn anything more.
那是因为你太懒了, 没办法再学新东西
Dr. Meredith Grey, Jeremiah Tate.
Meredith grey医生,这是jeremiah tate.
Thinks he knows so much because he was my first intern patient.
他自以为了解的很多
因为他是我做实习生 的时候第一个患者.
我和她懂的一样多.
I knew as much as her. She was clueless about how to treat cystic fibrosis.
她处理囊肿性纤维化 的时候笨的要命.
搞砸了一个简单的胆囊切除手术 让人家在医院呆了一个月
A cholecystectomy turned into a month-long stay.
你最好别被说成玩忽职守.
Better not be alleging malpractice.
这家伙参加三项全能赛, 一年内囊肿性纤维化100单位
Guy raises about 100,000 grand a year for cystic fibrosis, running triathlons.
我猜他一定是个大人物.
- Thinks he's a big shot. - You run triathlons?
你是三项全能选手??
- Why not? - Pain for one.
-不行吗? -一级疼痛.
看起来你终于承认 你感觉到点疼痛了
- Finally admitting to feeling a little? - A little.
-就一点吧. -多大一点?
How little? Truth.
说真话.
Enough to keep me awake at night.
嗯,只不过让我整夜无法入睡.
能感觉到在翻滚. Um...
Had some seizures. Too weak to work out.
但是我实在没力气抵抗了.
Anyone been through here with your CT results?
有人过来给过你 的C.T结果吗?
没有,我估计就是我的胰腺炎
No. It's probably just my pancreatitis kicking up again.
-又发作了而已. -明白了
All right then. We'll be back.
回头我们会拿来你的结果,以及解决方案的.
With your results and a plan.
这次你父母认为你 是在哪里了?
Where do your parents think you are this time?
新泽西.
[Chuckles] New Jersey.
他父母怎么办?
What about his parents?
他不愿意告诉他父母
He doesn't like to bother them until he's well or about to get discharged.
直到他恢复,或者要出院的时候.
他了解自己的情况
He understands his reality. He just chooses to ignore it.
他只不过选择不予理睬罢了 "否认"对他挺有用的, grey.
Denial works for him, Grey.
腹痛.腹痛.
"Abdominal pain."
"直肠脓肿. 头部枪伤."
"Perirectal abscess."
"Gunshot wound to the head."
头部枪伤是怎么他妈的回事?
Where the hell's this GSW to the head? Why wasn't the trauma team called?
为什么外伤科的人没来?
Hello? Are you people insane?
有人吗?你们都傻了啊?
你那枪伤受害者在那儿呢.
There's your gunshot victim.
他?
Him?
我正在重新把客厅铺上米色的丝绸,
I'm redoing the living room in beige silks, I'm thinking.
我在想.
And modern. Very mid-century.
时尚而具有中世纪的味道.
-还有餐厅... -妈,把我脚趾拿回来.
- And the dining room... - Mother, give me back my toes.
Okay. 我换个话题.
OK. I change the subject.
谁是爸爸?
- Who's the father? - Mid-century, did you say?
你是说你喜欢中世纪吗?
Someone you work with, right? Was it just for sex?
和你一起工作的人,对吧?
或者仅仅是打个炮而已?
你的想法真是不切实际
You make such a point of not forming attachments.
20分钟.留给我 20分钟的清净吧.
20 minutes. All I want is 20 minutes of peace and quiet.
我养的女儿应该感激 她妈妈的帮忙.
The daughter I raised would appreciate her mother's help.
你养的女儿正在恳求你 离开这里,马上!
The daughter you raised is begging for you to go. Now.
我根本没有义务来这里 你知道,我很忙
I didn't have to come here. You know I'm very busy.
我知道,真的,全知道, 你正在重新装修你的房子
Yeah, I know. Redecorating your house.
请你给我一杯摩卡咖啡可以吗?
Well, can you get me a mocha latte, please?
脱脂的.
A non-fat one.
不, 普通的.
No. A fat one!
嗯,你能走.
You're walking, you're talking, there's no exit wound.
你能说话,并没有太大的损伤.
这个标记看上去更像一个烧伤.
- This mark here looks more like a burn. - I'm telling you, I shot myself.
我告诉你了,我射到了我自己...
Pulled the trigger cleaning my.22. I thought the clip was out.
我在擦拭我的22的时候,扣动了扳机.
我以为弹膛已经拿出去了.
If you're thinking suicide, don't.
如果你正认为我是自杀的话,千万别,
People make mistakes. I made a mistake.
人人都会犯错,我也会...
我正为此付出代价.
And now I'm paying for it. But I did shoot myself.
但是我的确对自己开枪了.
你的监护医生呢?
- Where's your IV? - I'm taking solids. I Hep-Locked it.
我正在吃固体食物,正在消化着.
- On whose orders? - Mine.
-谁下的指令? -我自己.
OK. Yang.
Okay. "yang."
这个命令如何?"上床休息,
How about this order: "Bed rest, out of bed to chair, bathroom privileges."
"床和椅子之外,只可以去洗手间"
和你在护士站偷病历无关
Nothing about stealing charts.
Okay, 知道吗? Hey, hey, hey! 把这个给我.
OK, you know what. Hey. Give me that.
Ah. Ah. 这样满意了吗?
There. Satisfied? I'm "out of bed to chair."
我不在床上,在椅子上.
- I'm telling your intern on you. - Meredith?
-我会告诉你的监护实习医生的. -Meredith?
-Yeah. -哦,我好怕怕哦
- Yep. - Oh, I'm so scared.
Grey医生, 你好吗'?
- Dr. Grey, how are you doing? - You're here. Good.
你来了. 好.
I need the results of the barium esophagram or the EGD.
我需要你钡理化验的结果
或者e.g.d.,但是你什么都没给我,Okay.
And you have neither. OK, no worries. I'll be here when you get back.
不用担心,你回来的时候我会在这里的.
今天你是她的实习生?
So today you're her intern. Well, that's better than being her husband.
嘿嘿,比做她老公好多了.
- That's a matter of opinion. - Good morning, Ellis.
这只不过是看法不同的问题罢了.
早上好, ellis.
Richard, good to see you. I need those labs immediately.
Richard, 见到你真好. 我现在就需要那些结果.
头儿, um...
Chief? She's not a surgical patient anymore.
她不再是个等待接受手术的病人了,
And I'd really like to get back to the OR.
所以我更愿意回到手术室去
So, do you think I could hand her off to someone else?
嗯,你觉得我能把她 交给其他人吗?
O'malley, alzheimer导致她 颠倒黑白
O'Malley, Alzheimer's causes her reality to shift depending on situation or mood.
全凭当时的情况,以及她的心情.
She needs stability right now.
她此刻需要的是稳定下来.
That's why I'm depending on you to keep a special eye on her.
这就是为什么我相信你 让你对她特殊照顾
是的,我知道,但是先生,那个..,
Yes, I know, sir.
But, you know, it just doesn't seem fair to me.
这样看起来对我不是很公平.
I need those studies yesterday.
我需要昨天的那些病例.
你听到医生说什么了.
You heard the doctor.
去吧.
Get moving.
我看到了.
I saw that. I saw you take that pill.
我看到你吃药了.
oh.那个是..我的药丸. 那个.."药丸"
Oh, it's my pill. You know, the pill.
这个并不在你的病历上,
It's not in your chart. You're supposed to tell us all the meds you're on.
而且你应该告诉我们 你正在服用的所有药物.
You're not my doctor. You shouldn't even be here.
你不是我的医生.
-你甚至不应该在这里. -她说的对.
- She's right. You shouldn't be here. - She took unauthorized medication.
你不应该在这里.
我看到她在吃不知名的药品.
I'm on the pill and I had grapefruit juice this morning.
我一直在吃这药丸,
我今早喝了柚子汁
Since the juice inhibits enzymes involved in the metabolism of OCPs,
因为果汁抑止?的分泌,
所以会影响ocps(口服避孕药)的新陈代谢
I avoided the interaction by taking it two hours after food.
我想避免交叉作用
所以我在饭后两个小时之后吃.
She has a doctorate in neuropharmacology.
她是神经药理学医生, cristina.
- I don't see oral contraceptives. - Guys.
-Well, izzie, 我没看到什么口服避... -你们.
Now you will. Go back to bed and stop poaching my patients?
-Okay, 好了你现在应该. -你可以回到你床上去吗...
-你可以回到你床上去吗 -别在打我病人的主意了?
This is ridiculous! Go back to bed and stop poaching my patients!
才没有...
[Rapid beeping]
-她心脏停止了. -呼叫警报代码.
- She's in V-fib! - Call the code!
code blue,second floor.
- [PA] Code blue, second floor. - [Loud gasp]
Code blue.second choice
- Code blue, second floor. - [Coughs, inhales deeply]
- [Man] You got the code equipment? - It's all ready to go.
-不危险了? -没有了.
- No code? - Not anymore.
能帮我把她带回床上吗?
- Can you help us get her back in bed? - I'll help.
我可以帮忙,就等我一下.
[Lzzie] Would you just go back to bed? Go!
求你能不能上床? 我说真的,快回去
Oh,天, izzie, 如果她正在吃口服避孕药
Oh, God. You know, lzzie, if she's on OCPs, can we mark it down, OK?
那么我们记下来,好吗?
Yeah.
jeremiah在上腹部的中间有阴影,
[Meredith] Jeremiah's got a mass in his midepigastrium.
胰腺部位的扩散.
Diffused enlargement of the pancreas.
同时他患有低血糖...
That, with his hypoglycemic seizures...
他需要一个极度危险的 剖腹手术...
He's gonna need an exploratory laparotomy.
即使不考虑他的三项全能技术,
But, despite his triathlons, his lungs still make me hesitant to cut.
我还是犹豫是否要切除他的肺
我们该怎么办?
What are we going to do?
我现在还不知道
- I don't know that yet. - Doctors.
医生.
- Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd. - How old is he?
Montgomery-shepherd医生.
-他多大? -26岁.
- He's 26. - A survivor, huh?
-幸存者, huh? -一些吧.
And then some. My patient for at least five years.
做我的病人至少做了5年了.
- I'm not gonna lose him now. - You planning a laparotomy?
我现在不想失去他
你在计划剖腹手术?
Yeah, but his lungs.
-是啊,可是他的肺... -嗯,你知道
You know, I think I could help you with this.
这个我可以帮帮你.
I've seen one case like this in a nine-year-old.
我以前遇到过一个 类似的病例,是个9岁的孩子.
最后我们做了 整个胰脏的切除.
We had to do a total pancreatectomy.
对于你将给予我的任何 帮助我都非常感激.
I'd be honored to take any help you can give me.
你是婴儿专家. 那个... 我... 这好像不是你的专长
You're a neonatal specialist. What...
This isn't your area.
我的意思是说,我...
I'm just saying. I...
我在囊肿性纤维化方面 做了两年的遗传学研究
I did genetics research in cystic fibrosis.
我对这个还是挺了解的, Grey医生.
- I've pretty much seen it all. - Oh.
Oh.
[PA] Dr. Ramirez, please call extension 543.
仅仅因为她提供她一个帮助,
Just because she offered her services doesn't mean she intends to stay.
并不代表她就想留下来了.
- Well, what does it mean? - It means that she's a good doctor.
那你说这算什么? 因为对我来说...
这只是意味着她是个好医生.
[Laughs]
Oh ho ho.为什么你突然保护起她来了?
- Why are you suddenly defending her? - I'm not.
我没有. Meredith, 她把离婚协议给我了
Meredith, she gave me divorce papers. She filed.
而且她已经同意了.
Oh. Well, that's good.
Oh. 那不错.
我所应该做的就是签字,然后我就自由了.
All I have to do is sign, and I'm free.
我们都自由了.
We're free.
还有什么需要考虑的吗?
Is there anything to think about?
不,当然没有 我只需要研究一下条款,
No, of course not.
I read through them, sign, then Addison's on the next plane out of here.
签字,然后addison会搭 下一班飞机离开这里.
你说他在头上有枪伤?
- You say he got shot in the head? - He says he got shot in the head.
他说他射到了自己的头. 我觉得他精神有点问题.
I say he's a mental defect.
Um, hi.
- Hi. - Ma'am, you can't be in here.
-女士,你不能进来这里. -Yeah, 我知道.
I'm looking for Samuel Linden, he...
我在找 samuel linden. 他...
oh, 天啊. Samuel.那个, 怎么... 怎么...
Oh, my God. Samuel. Well, how bad is it?
-多... 到底有多糟糕? -你是他老婆吗?
- Are you his wife? - For 21 years. Just tell me how he is.
是了21年了都,你就告诉我他到底怎么了.
挺好的,作为一个说他自己射了自己的人.
Fine, for a man who says he shot himself.
他开枪射了自己,在擦拭枪的时候.
He shot himself. He was cleaning his gun. What is wrong with you people?
你们认为这有什么不对?
We'll know when we finish his CT.
昨晚CT之后我们才会知道怎么回事
- This is a restricted area, ma'am. - My husband has a bullet in his head!
-这里是员工区,女士请你离开. -不,不,我老公有颗子弹留在脑袋里了
如果你能呆在外面的话,我们将找到结果
Then we'll find it. Wait outside,
我发誓我一拿到结果 就会让你知道
I'll be with you as soon as we know something, I promise.
这城市里这么多好医生
Of all the fine doctors in the city, you accept a consult from Addison Shepherd?
-你竟然和addison shepherd会诊? -Montgomery-shepherd, 是吗?
- Montgomery-Shepherd, isn't it? - She should be on her way home.
重点是她应该已经在回去的路上了.
你在试着把我逼疯,是吗?
You're trying to drive me crazy, aren't you?
- [bell] - Hey, don't...
-Oh, hey, 现在别做这个. -你觉得我这个病例和你有什么关系吗?
You think this has something to do with you?
你认为我甚至考虑过你吗?
You think I'm even thinking about your romantic problems?
以及你的爱情问题?
I'm trying to help a patient very near and dear to my heart.
我在试图帮助一个 和我非常亲近的病人,
如果需要会诊的话 和你的妻子,或者前妻,抑或情妇,
And if consulting with your wife, your ex, your mistress,
不管她是什么身份 如果这是个问题的话
whatever she becomes, if that's what's needed to save my patient,
我还是会努力去挽救我的病人 不计代价的.
- then I'm damned well going to do it. - I understand that.
我明白.
I deserved that. It's...
我罪有应得.只是... 算了,只不过...
Look, you have put yourself between two very fine women
听着,你把你自己放在 两个非常好的女人中间
现在你在试图寻找个简单的方法解决.
and you're looking for an easy way out.
你要用我,或者医院...
You want to use me, the hospital,
或者什么其他人来替你做决定.
somebody to make the decision for you, and it's not gonna happen!
不会成功的.
我可以...
- Could I just say a couple of things? - Just...
-可以让我说一点其他的吗? -别... deh, deh, deh.
你有点吓倒我们了.
You scared us a little there. How's her work-up coming?
她的结果如何?
Electrolytes are within normal limits, urine tox was negative and EKG's fine.
Uh, 电解液正常,
尿氧阴性,e.k.g正常.
Tilt test is scheduled for noon. Oh, and she's on contraceptives.
Tilt测试预约在中午.
Oh,还有她正在吃避孕药.
- So? - That's what I said.
-那又如何? -我也这么问.
That other doctor made such a big deal of it.
另外一个医生对此惊讶不已.
Well,她以前并没有提起.
She didn't tell us before. So I documented it in her med list.
现在我记在她的药物史上了.
什么另一个医生?
- What other doctor? - Cristina. She was wandering the halls.
Cristina.她曾在大厅里闲逛.
好吧,带她下去做个回波.
Fine. Take her down for an echo.
回波? 复律法或者切除术如何?
An echo? What about cardioversion or ablation?
我不需要个心脏起博器 或是内部的永久去纤颤器?
Won't I need a pacemaker or a permanent internal defibrillator?
虽然对风湿性心脏病 来说并不常见
Although it would be unusual for rheumatic heart disease
但它可能是导致心律不齐的原因,
to cause ventricular dysrhythmias, we've still got to check your valves.
我们还是会检查一下你的气阀.
我以为你的博士学位 是在药理学领域
I thought your doctorate was in neuropharmacology, not medicine.
-不是临床医学. -就是.
It is.
好消息是Addison给了derek 离婚协议书.
Addison gave Derek divorce papers, which is good.
我是说,她还在这里做她的addison,
I mean, she's still here, being Addison, but it's not like I'm jealous.
但是这并不代表我是嫉妒或者什么.
- That's odd. - It's odd that I'm not jealous?
-这个不成对. -我不嫉妒是不成对的?
不是,你绝对有权嫉妒.
No, you have every right to be jealous.
这是你的地盘,她却到处惹事.
It's your territory and she's peeing all over it. What's odd is Burke's patient.
burke的患者竟然不成对的.
Four other hospitals this year. Something's not right.
她今年内还住过其他4家医院.
肯定有什么事情不对.
- Why the interest in Burke's patient? - This has nothing to do with Burke.
你起来对burke的病人 十分有兴趣啊
和 burke无关.
You lost a fallopian tube, a baby, and a boyfriend all in one day.
Cristina,你失去了一个输卵管,一个孩子
还失去了一个男朋友,都在同一天里.
You have the right to be upset.
你绝对有权难过.
You're losing McDreamy to his wife. You have a right to be jealous.
而你正在失去你的"美梦先生" 因为他完美的妻子也在这里.
你也有权嫉妒
I did not lose McDreamy. Divorce papers, remember? And I'm not jealous.
我没失去我的"美梦先生".
离婚协议,记得吗? 还有我根本不嫉妒.
我也不难过.
- And I'm not upset. - You really should be in your room.
你真应该回到你的病房去
If this was reversed, would you want to spend time with your mother
okay, 如果情况调换,
你会不会愿意
in a confined room with one window?
和你妈妈一起被关在 一个只有一扇窗户的小房间里?
你觉得我们喜欢他们吗?我们的老妈?
Do you think we're like them? Our mothers?
[Announcement over PA]
James医生...
-你妈妈在哪里? -对极了.
Uh, where's your mom?
Exactly. Where is my mother?
-我妈在哪里? -你妈在哪里?
- Where's your mother? - Funny you should ask.
真有意思你问对了.
Oh, crap.
Oh, 糟了.
Oh, man, you are not going to believe this.
Oh,伙计,你不会相信这个的.
不,不可能
No. It can't be. The guy was reading a freaking magazine.
那家伙读一本奇怪的杂志.
It's definitely a bullet. Tracked clear through his head.
绝对是一颗子弹,
一颗沿着清晰的轨迹穿过他的大脑.
你们是想继续傻坐在这里
Now are you people just going to sit here or get him into surgery?
还是立刻动手术?
你能看到这就是那子弹的痕迹,
Here's the missile track. As you can see it doesn't even cross the midline.
还没穿过中线,他真幸运.
He's lucky. This guy may have even been sitting there talking to you.
她在那里
这人可能还可以 坐在那里和你聊天.
He'll need debridement of the entrance wound and repair the dura,
他的手术需要穿过他的伤口 在内部修复创伤的脑膜
但是我们并不需要取出子弹.
but we won't need to remove the bullet.
精彩的诊断Grey医生.
That's an excellent diagnosis, Dr. Grey.
我是Shepherd医生.我是你的同僚.
I'm Dr. Shepherd, I'm your neuro consult.
Grey医生...
Dr. Grey, they need you upstairs.
楼上的人需要你过去.
你去预定手术室和放射检查?
- You'll book the OR and staff? - I'm on it.
我来.
不可思议.
- Unbelievable. - O'Malley.
O'malley.
Can you not handle this, doctor?
你能不处理这个吗,医生?
好多事情我处理不了.
I can handle a lot of things. Wheelchairs. Come on, Dr. Grey.
没做手术我们是没有把握肯定如此
[Addison] We won't know for sure until we go in there,
但是看起来很像
but it looks like I'm gonna have to take out your pancreas
我要摘除你的胰脏
and re-route your intestines.
并且做肠绕道.
Did you tell her my lungs don't do well with anesthesia?
你告诉她我的肺 不太适应麻醉了吗?
我不是一直有你的资料吗?
Don't I always have your back?
你的肾功能衰竭的很快,
Your kidney function is decreasing and I'm afraid
恐怕你会患有多重器官衰竭
you'll go into multi-system organ failure if we don't operate.
如果我们不做这个手术的话.
- If I say no? - There's no guarantees, Jeremiah.
如果我说不做呢?
这并没有任何保障,jeremiah.你知道这个.
这将会是一个漫长而艰难的手术
It's going to be a long, hard surgery, and put a lot of stress on your body.
你的身体会承受很大压力.
Yeah, but I'm me.
对,但是我还是我.
但是你还是你
- But you're you. - So if we don't operate, I die.
所以如果我不做手术,我就会死
如果我做了手术,我可能还是会死.
And if we do operate, I may die.
基本上来说,对.
Basically, yes.
我喜欢这个失败几率.
Well, I like those odds.
26岁就得了这个病,我真牛,
And 26 years with this disease is awesome. And that's the reality.
这是事实.
So if I get lucky, great.
所以如果我幸运的话,没话说,
如果我不幸的话...
If I don't...
真贴心.
it's been sweet.
我会一直陪着你,一直贴心的.
It's gonna stay sweet.
你理解吗,我们需要 做一个心理评估?
[Derek] We'll need to do a psych evaluation.
我们还需要告诉你几次?
How many times do we have to tell you? He wasn't trying to kill himself.
他并没有想要自杀.
-那是个意外. -他们只是做自己的工作而已, hon.
- It was an accident. - They're just doing their job, hon.
不,他们的工作是让你好起来.
- Their job is to make you better. - Where were you at the time?
枪响的时候你在哪里?
I was in the next room. And I heard the shot. And it was awful.
我在隔壁房间,
-我听到了枪声,真是太可怕了. -Mm-hmm. 抓住这个.
现在都结束了.
- It's over now. - [Alex] Why didn't you call 911?
你为什么没报警?
Because he was only unconscious for a moment.
因为他只是昏迷了一小会 然后就...
然后他就.. 可以走 可以说话...
And then he was walking, and talking and...
你应该去报告警察.
You'll have to give a report to the police.
警察?
- Police? - Why do we need to talk to the police?
我们..我们应该和警察说什么?
We have to report any gunshot wounds to the police. It's the law.
我们需要向警察报告 任何一个枪伤患者
是法律.
没事的.
你真是 a.w.o.l.,知道吗.
You're officially AWOL, you know.
我在工作呢,我要做出来
I'm working. Trying to figure out what's going on with the crazy woman on four.
到底那去了4家医院的疯女人怎么回事.
You are the crazy woman on four.
你就是那疯女人.
I made a break for freedom. Hand me that dictionary.
我只是为了自由小小休息一下.
你能把那字典给我吗?
你有一个比我好的病人,
[Sighs] You have a better patient than me and you don't even have a patient.
你甚至没有病人.
Meredith's got a CF case. Alex's got the gunshot wound.
Meredith有个 c.f.患者, alex有个枪伤患者,
izzie的患者是神秘的心律不齐.
Izzie's got the mystery arrhythmias. I'm not a nanny.
我并不是个保姆,我是个医生,做手术的医生
I am a surgeon. A cutter.
但是,我现在却得到假标签
But no, I'm getting fake labs for a fake patient so she can do a fake surgery.
因为一个假患者, 这样她就可以做一个假医生
她是装出来的.
- She's faking it. - It's real to her. It's Alzheimer's.
对她来说都是真的,alzheimer's.
传教士,Kalpana.
The missionary. Kalpana...
oh,天啊
[groans] God! Thank you!
-谢谢. -Ow.
Ow!
没必要.
Uncalled for!
- Izzie. How have her studies been? - I've been looking for that everywhere.
-Hey, izzie,她的进展如何? -Hey, 我到处找那病历.
阴性, 对吗?
Negative, right?
Oh, 回波测试显示 只是轻微的二尖瓣狭窄而已.
Oh! The echo test showed mild mitral stenosis, the tilt test was negative.
tilt测试也是阴性. 我们正在做 e.p.测试.
We're doing EP studies.
我能告诉你她到底怎么了
I know what's wrong without sticking electrodes in her heart.
而且不用把电极粘到她的心里.
是吗? 就凭病历.
- Really. Just by the chart? - No, from the pill she took.
不,凭她吃的药.
They were contraceptives. Why are you so obsessed with this? Just go back to bed.
那是避孕药,cristina.
你为什么对这个如此执着? 回到你的床上去.
-我觉得她是在自己骗自己 -你觉得她自己在
- She's doing this to herself. - Inducing ventricular arrhythmias?
诱导心律不齐? 她一定是疯了才这么做.
- She'd have to be crazy. - No, she'd have to have Munchausen's.
不,不,不,不. 她只是需要夸大其词.
Okay, 等一下,你觉得她 在偷偷的吃下什么东西
Wait. You think she's secretly ingesting something to produce real symptoms?
来制造出真正的征兆?你认真的吗?
- Seriously? - Yep. Just run it by Burke.
对,告诉burke这件事, 然后再回来告诉我他怎么想的.
- Tell me what he thinks. - Tell him yourself. He's behind you.
你自己告诉他吧,他就站你后面呢.
Burke医生.
[Husband and wife talk quietly]
我们说到哪里了?
- Where are we? - OR Two in 30 minutes.
2号手术室,30分钟之后 他准备好了,差不多到时候了.
He's prepped, transpo's on the way.
[Woman] Do you understand that? 21 years!
21年
- What's that all about? - I haven't got a clue.
-那是什么? - 多少次
-我也没线索 -需要我道歉吗?
I love you. I forgive you.
我爱你,okay?我原谅你.
你竟然搞外遇,你搞外遇,
You cheated on me. You cheated on me.
你用不着在这里装烈士
- You do not get to play the martyr. - I got a bullet in my head.
-我脑子里有颗子弹. -即使这样也无法让我俩平衡.
- And that doesn't make us even. - You shot me!
你向我开枪.
I think we need to get the police up here right now.
我想我们应该 现在就把警察叫来.
我是说,很明显她喜欢扮演病人.
She obviously loves the patient role. She practically lives in hospitals.
就是说她实践住院
And we're like an imaginary family to her
同时...我们这些人 好像是她的假想家人一样
因为她真正的家庭放弃了她
because her real family blows her off to go take care of other people.
而去照顾其他人
- And I saw her take something. - That's not enough.
我看到了她在吃什么药片.
这还不够.
We have to rule out everything else.
我们必须排出其他所有的可能 所有的身体方面患病的可能.
她甚至胡诌了一个职业. 她是药剂师方面的,
She lied about her job. She's a pharmacy tech, not a Ph.D.
-不是博士. -所以她是个骗子,我以前也被骗过.
So she's a liar. I've been lied to before.
喂,我们不能在这里谈这个.
- We're not talking about us here. - Maybe we should be.
-也许我们可以. -我没撒谎.
- I didn't lie. - You withheld the truth.
-你一直隐藏真相,我如何能知道... -好,知道吗?
OK, you know what? I remember you breaking things off with me.
我很清楚的记得 是你先提出和我分手的,
而你并没有因为这个而难过.
You didn't seem so upset about it. This? This is not a relationship.
Okay, 这个... 这不是... 这不是拍拖.
-这不是真的. -Cristina.
- This is not real. - Cristina!
Okay, 那么... 那么即使假扮受伤的戏剧,
OK, and so what's with the big fake display of hurt and drama?
又有什么大不了的?
-Cristina. -我应该躺在床上.
- Cristina! - I'm supposed to be in bed.
Cristina.
Cristina!
警官,谢谢您赶来.
Officers, thanks for coming.
女士,您能坐下吗?
Ma'am, why don't you have a seat? We need to ask you a few questions.
我们需要问你一些问题
Oh, 嗯,当然.
Uh, of course.
看起来并不像是场家庭内战
Well, nothing like a domestic dispute to liven up a pre-op, huh?
导致的一个大手术,嗯?
我应该在哪里签字?
- [Jeremiah] Where do I sign? - [Bailey] Here, for consent.
这里,同意签字..
这里是同意d.n.r的签字. 不需要额外抢救.
And here for DNR and no extraordinary measures.
很好,请抬起来一下.
[Bailey] Good. OK, lift up for me.
Ow. 你真应该 把我父母叫来.
You should probably call my parents.
你出院的时候自己叫.
Call them yourself when you walk out of here.
Grey医生, 我拿到了这些结果...
Dr. Grey, I have those labs...
oh, 不,你没有.
Oh, no you didn't. You lost her again? Again?
你又把她丢了?再一次?
我是个医生,医生.
I am a surgeon. A surgeon!
Yeah, 是啊.当webber医生 发现你又把ellis grey丢了的时候
[Chuckles] Yeah, well.
You won't be when Dr. Webber finds out you lost Ellis Grey again.
你就不是个医生了
[Laughs]
[Beeping]
我们正在使用3种不同的导管.
We're using three different catheters. Why are we doing that, Dr. Stevens?
为什么这么做,Stevens医生?
Programmed electrical stimulation maps the heart's electrical system
检验电极刺激
绘图心脏的电极系统
- to find the focus of the irregular... - Doctors? Sorry to interrupt.
-来找出不规则的中心... -um, 医生?
-打扰一下. -嗯.
- [Burke] Yes? - Her urine's blue.
她的尿样是蓝色的.
什么?
What?
为什么她尿样是蓝色的?
Why is her urine blue?
她说她预约了shepherd医生 的一个手术.
She says she has a surgery scheduled with Dr. Shepherd?
我只不过转身5分钟而已.
- I turned my back for... - Why did you turn your back?
为什么你转身离开?
I told you to take care of her!
我告诉过你照顾她.
你走吧.
Just get out of here.
你想找个带劲的手术,那去找吧.
You want to find a hot surgery, then find one.
没你事儿了,我会照顾她的
You're free.
I'll take care of her.
这是个有病的混蛋.
[Alex] This is one sick bastard. We should flip him over, give him a spine.
真应该射穿他,然后刺他一刀.
Karev医生,把牵引器向后拉.
Pull back on the retractor, Dr. Karev. A little suction.
小吸血器?
Covering for his wife after she shot him?
替他老婆遮掩开枪射他
他在外面搞外遇.
- He did cheat on her. - And that's worth a bullet in the head?
对啊,这罪行够 吃颗子弹的了?
感情是建立在牺牲的基础上的.
Relationships are built on sacrifice.
-但不是这种牺牲. -Mm, 我不知道.
- Not that kind of sacrifice. - I don't know.
有时子弹值这个了.
Sometimes a bullet's worth it.
Oh, richard.
Richard, I thought you'd never get here.
我以为你永远不会来这里呢. 看呢,手术室是空的.
Look, the OR's empty, I have a little time before my surgery.
手术之前我还有一点时间.
我不认为我应该来这里
I don't think I'm supposed to be here.
不.
No.
不,你不应该.
No, you're not.
来吧,我带你回病房去
Come on, I'll take you back to your room.
我需要更多的牵引,grey医生.
[Bailey] I need more traction. Dr. Grey?
这里,帮我多抽入一下.
Here, give me some suction there.
现在, grey,把十二指肠放回去.
Grey, retract the duodenum. Good.
好,他怎么样?
How's he doing?
呼吸更困难.
- Hard to ventilate and no urine output. - He's shutting down.
-从我们开始就没排过尿. -他快不行了.
你加大他的压力峰值了吗?
- Did you increase peak pressures? - Any higher, I blow his lungs.
最高了已经,他的肺很受伤.
Bradycardia. Pushing one of atropine.
-心博减慢了. -注射一个单位的阿托品.
试试手动鼓风.
[Addison] Try ventilating him manually, see if he starts coming back up.
看他是否能开始好转.
- [Bailey] Did we miss any bleeders? - Surgical field is clear.
-我们错过什么细节了吗? -过程完全没错.
濒死迹象.
- Agonal rhythm. - [Bailey] Any pulse with that?
-有什么脉搏吗? -颈动脉没反应.
- [Anesthesiologist] No carotid. - Starting CPR. Push one of epi.
Okay, 开始心肺复苏术,注视一单位epi
不用额外抢救了,Bailey医生. 他签了d.n.r.
No extraordinary measures, Dr. Bailey. He's DNR.
这是好药啊.
No, this is just good medicine.
[Rapid beeping]
蓝色尿样?
Blue urine?
二级药物检查为阿莫曲替林阳性.
A second drug screen was positive for amitriptyline,
我知道你了解 这个就是造成心律不齐的原因.
which, I'm sure you know, causes ventricular arrhythmias.
你明白一般性的药物检查中 这个结果不会显示,
You knew it wouldn't show on a drug screen,
但是我猜你并没有意识到
but I'm guessing you didn't realize it turns urine blue.
它可以让你的尿变蓝.
I didn't do this to myself. You have to believe me. I'm sick.
这不是我自己做的.
你们要相信我,我有病.
我生病了,而且我还...
- I have something... - No. You're just deceiving yourself.
没有,你只是欺骗自己而已...
你根本没病,
Manufacturing things that really aren't there, seeing only what you want to see.
你只是看到你期望看到的东西...
浪费我们的时间,资源
Wasting our time, our resources, and throwing away your own life.
而且还在放弃你自己的生命.
你的病在你的脑子里kalpana.
Your illness is in your head, Kalpana.
我们会把你转到精神科.
We will be transferring you to Psych.
[Rapid beeping]
来吧.
Come on.
快点,别放弃.
Come on, don't give up. Come on.
-起来 -你累了.
You're getting tired. Let me take over, Dr. Bailey.
让我来继续,Bailey医生.
Bailey医生,他的肠已经青紫色了.
[Addison] Dr. Bailey, his intestines are cyanotic. There's no blood circulating.
血液停止循环了.
It's been shunted to his brain where he needs it. You call those compressions?
血液只不过都跑到 最需要的脑子里而已.
你把这个叫做压吗?
1, 2, 3...
[Grunts]
[Rapid beeping]
继续战斗.
Fight it. Come on!
来啊.
为什么没人动啊?
Why isn't anyone moving? Who's recording?
谁在记录?
It's been ten minutes since we had a perfusing rhythm.
我们已经做心肺复苏10分钟了
Bailey医生,你来宣布吧.
It's your call, Dr. Bailey.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
- [continuous beep] - One, two, three...
抢救无效.
Asystole.
[Beeping stops]
死亡时间... 19:26.
Time of death: 19:26.
当你很接近的时候 很难接受结束.
[Sighs]
It's hard to accept the end when you're too close.
听着,我不需要一个不想要我的人 meredith,
Look, I don't want someone who doesn't want me, Meredith.
但是如果即使有万分之一 的希望他可能会...
But if there's the slightest chance that he does, I'm not leaving Seattle.
我不会离开西雅图的.
她怎么和警察说的?
What did she tell them?
你背着她搞外遇, 然后她喝醉了,
That you cheated on her, that she was drunk,
当时你正在厨房里面擦枪.
and you were cleaning your guns in the kitchen.
我不会指控她的.
- I'm not gonna press charges. - It doesn't matter, she confessed.
没关系.
她已经承认了,一级袭击.
- Assault in the first degree. - They arrested her?
他们逮捕她了?
Man, you should be grateful.
伙计,你应该谢天谢地.
知道我是什么吗?我是傻瓜.
You know what I am?
I'm stupid.
没有比欺骗爱你的女人
Nothing is more stupid than cheating on the woman you love.
更傻的事情了
You don't know what you're missing.
你不知道你失去了什么.
你的摩卡咖啡在你床边,
Your latte's by your bed, and I'm pretty sure it's cold.
我很确定那已经凉了
我不需要了.
- [Exhales] I don't need it. - You should be in bed.
你应该躺在床上.
Stop it. I'm fine, OK? My brain is fine. My body is fine. I'm fine.
省省吧,我很好,ok?
我的脑子很好,我的身体很好,总之很好.
-真不知道我为什么来. -那你为什么来了啊?
- I don't know why I came. - Then why did you?
你知道.我很...那个,算了别说了.
You know, I... Just stop it. I don't...
我不... 对不起我不是那种人.
I'm sorry I'm not that person. I'm sorry I don't need you here taking care of me.
对不起,我不需要你的照顾
-怎样? -你说对了.
Well?
You were right. Kalpana definitely suffers from Munchausen's.
Kalpana的确在夸大其词.
明白了? 我就是对的.
See. I was right.
我对了.
I was right.
我对了
我对了,对了..
I was right. I was... [sniffs] I was right.
对的,我对了..
I was right.
Oh,我..我,,
Oh, I'm...
我对了....我...
[bawls] I'm right...
我对了.我...
I'm right... I'm...
你在你的医学测试当中,
You took the Clinical Skills section of your medical exams after most interns,
临床学部分低于其他实习生.
结果刚刚出来.
so the results are only now coming out.
今早我接到 u.s.m.l.e.(西雅图医科学院)的电话.
I got a call from USMLE this morning.
Oh. 那你的意思..是说...
Oh.
So you're saying...
karev, 你仍然是医学博士
Karev, you're still an MD. You still get to practice medicine.
你仍然需要医学实践.
医院同意你四个月 后进行补考
The hospital grants you four months to retake the exam.
你学习,你通过了,你才能把这些放过去.
You study it, you pass it, you put it behind you.
一次失误并不会影响你的职业生涯.
One misstep doesn't affect your career.
Yeah.对对对,谢谢,谢谢
Right, thanks. Thanks.
en,那个,如果我参加补考的时候
What happens if I take the exam for a second time and I don't pass?
又没通过的话,会怎样?
你再也不能留在这医院做医生了
You will no longer be a surgical resident at Seattle Grace.
再不及格可不是一个选择.
Failing again is not an option.
[Wailing]
怎么了?
- What's going on? - I can't stop. I can't... I can't stop.
我停不下来,我停不下来.
哭.她无法停止哭了.
Crying. She can't stop crying.
我当然看的到,你们对她做了什么
I can see that. What did you do to her?
什么都没有
Nothing.
她快哭脱水了.
She's going to dehydrate. Cristina, do you want some water?
Cristina, 想喝点水吗?
不不不.
No. No.
-不! -不!
[Both] No!
我已经试过了,只会让情况更糟.
I already tried that. It just made it worse.
我知道她或早或晚都会崩溃的 不过是时间的问题.
I knew she'd break sooner or later. Just a matter of time.
我要杀了她!
I will kill her!
我是她妈妈.
I am her mother.
我们这里对待妈妈不是太好.
We don't do well with mothers here. Why don't you leave and come back later?
你为什么不离开一下过会再回来?
Cristina.
让这停止..让这停止啊
Make it stop. Make it stop.
谁给我点镇静剂!
Somebody sedate me! [sobs]
有时候, 现实有点鬼祟
[Meredith] Sometimes reality has a way of sneaking up and biting us in the ass.
在我们背后袭击我们...
当大坝决口的时候,
And when the dam bursts all you can do is swim.
你所能做的,就是游泳
伪装的世界是一个鸟笼,而不是蚕茧.
The world of pretend is a cage, not a cocoon.
我们只能跟自己长时间的撒谎.
We can only lie to ourselves for so long.
[& Merrick: Infinity]
我们都很疲惫.
We are tired. We are scared.
我们也很恐惧.
Denying it doesn't change the truth.
否认并不能改变事实.
Hi. Tate太太?
Hi, Mrs. Tate?
我是miranda.Miranda bailey.
It's Miranda. Miranda Bailey.
我打电话是因为jeremiah.
I'm calling about Jeremiah.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
她不想被碰
She doesn't want to be touched.
或迟或早,我们必须 把我们的否认放一边
[Meredith] Sooner or later, we have to put aside our denial
面对迎面而来的世界,炙热的燃烧
and face the world head-on, guns blazing.
Hi.
- Hi. - Hey.
-Hi. -你看起来不错.
- You look great. - Thanks.
谢谢
- Are you OK? - Yeah, you ready to go?
Yeah.
-你没事吧? -嗯,可以走了吗?
Yeah, 你... 你只是... 你看起来不太像你自己了.
Yeah, you just... You don't seem like yourself.
不. Uh, 我们预定了晚餐的位置了.
No. Look, we got dinner reservations. We should go so, let's go.
我们应该走了. 那么, uh...
OK.
-走吧. -Okay.
[Meredith] Denial. It's not just a river in Egypt. It's a freaking ocean.
否认... 不仅仅只是埃及的一条河流而已.
那是个怪异的海洋.
真高兴我们这样
I'm glad we're doing this.
我也是,想喝点什么吗?
Me too. Want a drink?
Yes. Oh.
- Yes. Oh... - That's OK, I got it.
-我来 -我来.
I'll get it.
那么你如何从中逃生呢?
[Meredith] So how do you keep from drowning in it?
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译:Parry Wong (澳洲) 校对:Parry Wong (澳洲)
Grey's Anatomy S204 风软论坛 荣誉出品 www.1000fr.com